1990년 몬타나주, 뷰트
다쳤어
She's hurt!
누가 911에 신고해줘요!
Someone call 911!
비켜주세요
제가 의사입니다
Stand back.I'm a doctor.
자 어디 한번 보자
All right, sweetie.Okay.
갈비뼈가 부러진 것 같네요
She may havebroken some ribs.
부모님이 누군지 아십니까?
Anybody know her parents?
병원으로 데려가야겠어요
All right, I'm gonna take herto the hospital.
일으키는것 좀 도와주세요
Help me get her up.
조심하렴
이제 괜찮단다
Easy.Easy.That's it.It's okay, sweetie.
행운을 빈다
Good luck.
진짜 아팠어요
That really hurt.
손목이 삔 것 같아요
I think I sprained my wrist.
경상인데 뭐
Well, it's just aflesh wound, darling.
병원 갈래?
I can take you to thehospital,
아님 록키 로드 먹을래?
(아이스크림 이름)
or I canget you some Rocky Road?
네가 결정하렴
Choice is yours.
록키 로드요
Rocky Road.
우리 얼마나 벌었어요?
So, how much we get?
네가 세볼래?
Want to count it?
5달러, 10달러..
20달러 맞네요. 고맙습니다
SARAH:Five and ten makes 20.Thank you.
좋은 하루 보내세요
Have a nice day.
힘들어요?
Long day?
지루하네요
Boring day.
새라 맘에 들만큼
재밌을진 모르겠지만
Well, not sureif it's the excitementthat you're looking for,
누나네 커플하고
가짜 데이트 안할래요?
but, uh, you wantto come over tonightfor a fake datewith Awesome and Ellie?
스킨쉽은 가짜겠지만
피자는 진짜예요
I promise fake cuddling, but real pizza.
미안해요, 척
I'm sorry, Chuck.
계획이 있어요
I- I have plans.
오늘 밤에 작전 있어요?
Is there a mission tonight?
전 얘기 못 들었는데요
I- I don't remembergetting the memo.
아뇨
Uh, no.
작전 없어요
그냥 계획이 있어요
No mission.Just plans.
그렇겠죠
Of course.Plans.
다른 28세 싱글 스파이들이
가질만한 계획이요
Like any other single28-year-old spywith an eveningto herself would have.
미안해요
개인적인 일이라서요
I'm sorry, Chuck, but it's personal.
케이시
오늘 작전 준비됐어요?
So, uh, ready for thebig mission tonight?
- 무슨 작전?
- 모르는척 할거 없어요
-What mission?
-You don't have toplay games, okay?
새라하고 무슨 커다란
비밀 작전 하는거 알아요
I know.You and Sarah--super secret mission.
작전 없어, 멍청아
There's no mission, moron.
할 일이 있대서 쉬는거지
She's taking a personal day.
그런 날도 있는지 몰랐는데요
I didn't realize wegot personal days.
응 넌 없어
우리만 있지
Well, you don't.We do.
새라 뭐하러 가는지 알아요?
Any idea what she's up to?
뭔데요?
Well?
개인적인 일이야
It's personal.
지금 뭐하는거야?
What do you think you're doing?
우리 둘이 하는데
다른 사람이 못 보게 하려는거지
Giving us a little privacyso we can hook up.
이리와봐
Come here.Come on.
모건, 싫어
Morgan!No!
여기서만 그러는것도 지겨워
I'm sick of hooking uponly at work.
나도 다른데 가면 좋겠지만
어디로 가?
Ah, I'd love to go someplace else, but where?
우리 엄만 항상 집에 계시고
넌 룸메이트가 셋이나 되잖아
My mother's always home, you have three roommates.
좋은 생각 있으면 말해봐
I mean, I'm opento suggestions.
정말?
Really?
잘됐다. 여기
Good!Here.
부에나 버뱅크 아파트야
The Buena Burbank Apartments.
진짜 예쁜 방 하나가 비었대
They have really cuteone bedrooms.
나 여기 살 돈 없어
See, I can't afford this.
우리 둘이 내면 되지
We could together.
다음 단계로 넘어갈 때가 됐잖아
We're readyto take the next step.
우리가...
We...
그것 참..
That's, um...
엄청난 일이잖아
이런건 서두르지 말고
That's a very bigstep, you know, andI think that it's not somethingthat you should rush into.
우리 둘이서 상의를 해봐야지
I think that it's somethingyou should discuss.
아니 여길 좀 봐봐
I mean, look at thisplace, all right?
72인치 플라즈마, 편안한 쇼파
공짜 커피까지 있잖아
72-inch plasma, super comfy couches, all the free coffeewe can drink.
꿈 속에 사는 것 같은데 왜 그래
I mean, come on, baby.We are living the dream.
대체 누구 꿈인데?
Whose dream, Morgan?
모든 사람
Everyone's.
척, 네가 새라한테
부족한 남자라고 생각해본적 있어?
Hey, Chuck, you ever wonderif you're not man enoughto hang onto your woman?
나 너드허드 차가 필요해
I need a Nerd Herder.
안돼. 에밋이 뒷자리에서
제프 속옷을 찾았는데
No.Emmett found Jeff'sunderwear in the back seat,
혹시 모른다면서
위에 다시 천을 씌우는 중이야
and he's having them all re upholster ed as a safety precaution.
모건, 그럼 나 오토바이 좀 빌려줘
Okay, Morgan, I needto borrow your bike.
그래 알았어
써. 뭐하게?
Sure.Yeah, sure.Why?
개인적인 일이야
It's personal.
계획이 있다고?
Plans, huh?
대체 저 남자 몇 살이야?
How old is this guy?
자, 먹자
Let's eat.
저기, 잠시만요
Uh, excuse mejust a moment.
클램소스 링귀니로 주세요
Yes, I-I'd likethe linguiniwith the clamsauce, please.
난지 어떻게 알았어요?
How did you find me?
시계에 달린 GPS요
The GPS on your watch.
여기서 뭐하는거예요?
What are you doing here?
새라, 미안해요
Look, I'm-I'm sorry.
난 그냥 도와주러 온거예요
I came for backup only.
내가 개인적인 일이라고 했죠
I told you, it was personal.
알아요 알아요
근데 뭐가 떠올랐는데요
I know.I know, but I flashed.
새라, 나도..
Look, I'm all...
휴식이 필요하단거 나도 잘 알아요
그럴 자격 있고 말고요
I'm allfor a little time off, and God knows, you deserve it,
하지만 새라랑 같이 식사하고 있는
but I think that you should knowthat the much, much, much older gentleman
나이 무지 무지 많은 저 남자
정말 나쁜 사람이예요
that you're havingdinner with right nowis a very bad man, Sarah.
- 척
- 아직 안 끝났어요
-Chuck...
-Let me finish.
진짜 쓸모없는 사람이라니까요?
The guy is a total loser, all right?
남 등이나 쳐먹는 쓰레기예요
참, 나이도 엄청 많다고 얘기했나요?
Absolute bottom-feeding, scum of the earth, have I mentioned, considerably older man?
모두 맞아
그래도 나 춤은 끝내주게 춘다네
All true, but I'm a hell of a dancer.
척, 우리 아빠
잭 버튼씨세요
Chuck, I'd like youto meet my dad, Jack Burton.
아빠, 이 쪽은
제 남자친구 척이예요
Dad, this is my boyfriend, Chuck.
반갑습니다
A real pleasure, sir.
chuck
Season 02 Episode 10
Chuck 2x10
Chuck Versus the Delorean
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
영어자막 www.shooter.cn
한글번역 김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
Sync: YTET-텟텟
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON NBC : 2008/12/08
후렌치 토스트, 휘핑 크림
싱싱한 딸기야
French toast, whipped cream, fresh strawberries.
네가 좋아하는거잖니
Just howyou like them.
12살때 얘기죠
When I was 12.
그래도 뭐든 먹어야지
Well, you need to eat something.
직장에서 중요한 일 있다며
Big day at work.
뭐한다고 했더라?
What is it you'redoing again?
밀크 쉐이크 만든댔나?
Making milkshakes?
프로즌 요거트요
Frozen yogurt.
재밌겠구나
Sounds stimulating.
청구서 낼 만큼은 벌어요
Pays the bills.
그래, 알겠구나
Well, yeah, Ican see that.
참 믿을 만한 얘기야
Very believable.
그게 무슨 말씀이세요?
And what is thatsupposed to mean?
이 집, 네 직업, 네 이름
This place.Your job.Your name.
새라 워커?
어제 그 바보같은 놈은
Sarah Walker?That schnook fromlast night.
- 치피랬나?
- 척이요
-Chippy?
-Chuck.
무슨 일 벌이고 있는거잖아
You're workingan angle.
걔가 어디 비벌리 힐즈
부잣집 아들이라도 되는 모양이지?
I mean, he's probably the sonof some, uh, richBeverly Hills family?
척은 제 남자친구고, 시간당 12달러 벌어요
그니깐 관심 갖지 마세요
Look, Chuck is my boyfriend, and he makes $12 an hourso you stay away from him.
내가 끼어들지 말라는거지
알겠다
Hey, you don't wantto cut me in, fine.
걔 돈은 필요 없어
I don't need his money.
돈은 나도 있으니까
I got my own.
세상에
Oh, my God.
백만 달러는 되겠어요
That looks like almosta million dollars.
크리스마스가 좀 일찍 왔지
Well, Christmascame a little early.
가지렴
For you.
아뇨 됐어요
No, thanks.
아빠가 훔친 돈엔 관심없어요
I'm not interestedin your stolen money.
훔쳐? 넌 날 그렇게 생각하니?
싸구려 도둑?
Stolen?That's what you thinkof your old man, some two-bit thief?
얘, 도둑은 최대한
빨리 도망쳐야 하지만
Darling, a thief hasto run out of townas fast as he can,
하지만 실력있는 사기꾼은..
but a good con man...
자신이 원할 때
언제든지 떠날 수 있다구요
A good con man can leavewhenever he wants.
기억나요, 아빠
I remember, Dad.
어쨌든 이 돈 기부한 사람은 누구예요?
So, who donated the moneyanyway?
2달 전에 두바이에 갔었어
A couple months ago, I flew over to Dubai.
그 쪽에 있는 돈이
무슨 돈인지 넌 상상도 못할게다
You wouldn't believethe kind of moneythey got floatingover there.
이 돈은 쉐익 라지브 아마드가
선물로 준거야
This particular donation iscompliments of Sheik Rajiv Amad.
아마드?
사우디 석유 재벌가(家)요?
Amad?The Saudi oil family?
우리 딸이 아랍을 좀 아는구만
My daughter knows her Arabs.
저 일하러 가야겠어요
I got to go to work.
잊은거 없니?
forgetting something?
수고하렴
Have fun at the office.
모두 솔직하게 말씀드리면
SARAH:In the spiritof full disclosure,
저희 아빠께서 쉐익 라지브 아마드한테
거의 백만 달러를 사기치셨어요
my father has connedSheik Rajiv Amadout of nearlya million dollars.
크게 한탕 치셨구만
Hit the big time.
말씀만 하시면
여기로 모시고 오겠습니다
Give the order, and I'll bring him in.
네? 아버지를 체포하겠다는거예요?
What?!You're gonna arrestyour own father?
그거 이해 상충 뭐 그런거 아니예요?
Isn't that kind ofa conflict of interest?
워커 요원이 불편하다면
체포는 제가 맡겠습니다
If Agent Walker'suncomfortable, I'd be happy tomake the arrest.
아무도 체포되지 않을거야
No one is getting arrested.
아직은
Yet.
아마드는 수년간
CIA 테러 경계 리스트에 올라있었네
Amad's been on the CIA'sterror watch list for years.
아프가니스탄과 케냐의 테러 조직에
돈을 대준다는 혐의가 있어
He's suspectedof funding terrorist regimesin Afghanistan and Kenya.
최근 사진은 없고,
여러 가명들로 움직이네
We have no recent photos, and he goes by a numberof different aliases.
자네 아버지가 쉐익 재정 보유
상태를 알려주면 유용하게 쓰일게야
Any informationyour father could provideabout the sheik'sfinancial holdingswould be valuable intel.
장군님, 아버지는 제가
CIA 요원인걸 모르십니다
General, my father is unawareof my CIA career.
사실 좋아하실지도 잘 모르겠고요
In fact, I'm not surehe would be all that proud.
CIA요원인걸 밝히라 한 적없네
워커 요원
No one is asking youto compromise your cover, Agent Walker.
가서 아버지와 얘길 해봐
Just talk to your father.
인터섹트도 함께 데려가게
Take the Intersect with you.
장군님, 저희 아버진..
General, my father...
자네 아버진 연줄 많고
위험한 사람에게 사길 쳤어
Your father conneda very connected, very dangerous man.
쉐익이 알아차리기전에 아버지가
얼마나 연루되었나 알아보는게 좋을거야
You better find out how deephe's in before the sheik does.
모건
Captain Morgan.
안녕하세요
Hey, buddy.
척 봤어요?
Uh, have youseen Chuck?
일하러갔지
무슨 일인데?
Left for work.What's up?
무슨 일이냐구요?
What's up?
무슨 일이냐면
내 인생이 끝났어요
Basically, my life isover, that's what up.
준비됐어요?
You ready for this?
애나가 같이 살 아파트를 구하재요
Anna asked meto get an apartment together.
큰 발전인데
Big step, little man.
잘됐어
All right.
잘됀건지 잘 모르겠어요
I don't knowabout all right.
난..
I- I...
있죠, 전 아직
준비가 안된것 같거든요
You know what, man?I just don't thinkI'm ready for that.
지금도 좋단 말이죠
Things are good with us.
근데 뭐하러 일을 망쳐요?
You know, why-whyrock the boat?
솔직하게 말해도 돼?
Permission to speak freely?
우리 사이에 비밀이 어딨어요
There are nosecrets between us.
너한테 명예도 없고
인생 계획도 없고
Would you agreethat you have no credit, no life plan,
아파트도 차도
책임감도 없는다는거 동의하지?
no apartment, no car, no adult responsibilitiesof any kind?
그래도 아주 가끔은
제 빨래는 제가 해요
On rare occasion, I do my own laundry.
이젠 철 좀 들어야지, 모건
Time to grow up, Morgan.
저도 아는데
문제가 있어요
I know.Here's the thing.
아파트 사려면
돈도 많이 들잖아요
This apartment--it's a lot of dough.
그거 사면 빈털털이 되요
It'll clear me out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
돈이 좀 부족하면
우리가 빌려주면 되잖아
You're a little short on cash, you know, we'll lend it to you.
- 걱정할 것 없어
- 잠시만요
-Don't worry about it.
-Wait a minute.
그래주실 수 있어요? 정말요?
You'd do that for me?Really?
그럼
Yeah.
그렇담 정말 감사하죠
That's-That's super cool, man.
왜요?
Why?
그거야 널 믿으니까
Because I believe in you.
네 미래에 하는
투자라고 생각해줘
Consider it an investmentin your future.
정말 그렇게 생각하세요?
Are you...Are you sure about that?
응 그렇게 생각해
Yes, I'm sure.
게다가 다시 갚을거잖아
Besides, you'll pay me back.
매주 12%씩 이자 갚아
아니면 2%씩 올릴거야
12% interest every week, or it goes up two points.
그럼요
Absolutely.
- 어떻게 되는거예요?
- 2500달러면 되겠지
-What does that mean?
-$2, 500 should cover it.
자 받아, 모건
There you go, Morgan.
어른이 된걸 환영한다
Welcome to adulthood.
기다리고 있었어
We've been waiting for you.
새라가 장군님한테 한 말
그냥 하는 말이죠?
CHUCK:Sarah was just bluffingwith Beckman, right?
아니, 아버지를
체포하진 않을것 아니예요
I mean, she'd neverarrest her own father.
왜 안돼? 범죄자잖아
Why not?Guy's a criminal.
새라 평생 감옥을 들락날락 거린 사람이야
Been in and out of jailher whole life.
그래도 새라한테
신경 많이 쓰는 것 같던데요
But he...but heseems to care, though.
적어도 계속 가깝게
지내려고 하는것 같았어요
You know, Imean, at leasthe's attempting tohave a relationship.
난 우리 아버지가
어디 계신지도 모른단 말이예요
I don't even know wheremy own father is.
아 슬퍼라
Oh, that's sad.
넌 내가 네 예전 인생 신경 써주는
누구하고 헷갈리는 모양이지
You've confused me with someonethat cares about your lifebefore the Intersect.
대화 즐거웠어요
Good session, buddy.
우리 사이에 큰 발전이
생긴 것 같네요
Really feel likewe had a breakthrough there.
잘있어, 척
So long, Chuck.
그동안 재밌었지?
We had a goodrun, didn't we?
전설적이었지
Stuff of legend.
어디 가는데?
Where you headed?
어른 되러
Adulthood.
애나랑 같이 살기로 했어
Anna and I are moving intogether.
정말? 잘됐다!
축하해!
Really?That's fantastic!Congratulations, buddy.
응, 그래
아마도
Yeah.Yeah, I guess.
청춘을 즐겨, 찰스
Enjoy your youth, Charles.
한 순간도 낭비하지 말고
Enjoy every damnminute of it.
모건, 그 여자 봤어?
Dude, have you seen her?
누구? / 방금 가게로 들어온 섹시한 여자!
-Who?
-Just the hottest piece everto come intothis store!
사람도 아니야
Not even human.
진짜 섹시하다니까
Smoking hot.
어딨는데?
Where?
따라와봐
Follow your boys.
어서
1981 드로리언 DMC
1981 DeLorean DMC.
9000대만 생산된 그 차
Only 9, 000 made.
백 투 더 퓨처에 나온 그 차야
The exact car fromBack to the Future.
사실 그 영화에 나온 차는
포르쉐 엔진이 있었죠
Actually, theBack to the Futurecarhad a Porsche engine.
설치하는데 얼마나 걸리죠?
When's it goingto be done?
몇 주요
Few weeks.
적어도 몇 달이요
Months, at least.
아이팟 어댑터도 설치하니
잘 팔렸으면 좋겠네요
Well, hopefully theiPod adapter willhelp me sell it.
무슨 말씀이세요?
Are you serious?
이런 보물을 파는데
문제될게 뭐가 있겠어요?
How could you have any troubleselling this treasure?
조수석 문은 안 열리고 연비도 최악이예요
The passenger doordoesn't work, the gas mileageis horrible,
1시간에 22마일 이상 가면
꼼짝도 안하고요
and if it actually goesover 22 miles per hour, it stalls.
제가 살게요
I'll take it.
좋아요
Deal.
- 잘했어
- 그 사람 바보 아니라니까요
-Good boy.
-He's not a schnook!
자상하고 똑똑한 사람이예요
He's a wonderful caring, intelligent guy.
딱 봐도 바보구만
Who's a class A schnook.
끼어들지 말라는건 알겠는데
Look, you don't wantto cut me in, no problem.
내가 무슨 바본지 아니
But don't play mefor a fool.
계좌에 2200달러밖에 없더라
The guy has 2, 200 bucksto his name.
그걸 어떻게 아셨어요?
How do you know?
어젯밤에 ATM 카드 슬쩍했다
I lifted his ATM cardlast night.
네가 걱정되서
어떤 남잔지 확인 좀 해본거야
I wanted to check him out'cause I was worriedabout you.
그래서 돈 없는데 뭐요?
And now that you knowhe's broke?
이젠, 정말 걱정된다
Now, I'm really worried.
난 가서 택시 잡으마
I'm going to get a cab.
찰리, 왔구만
Charlie, there you are.
안녕하세요
Hi.
다시 뵈니 좋네요, 버튼씨
Good to see you again, Mr.Burton.
잭이라고 하게
Oh, please, please, Jack.
타이 멋지구만
Nice tie.
멋있군, 젊은이
Looking sharp, young man.
저 좋아하시는거 같아요
Well, I think he's warming upto me.
이게 우연히
아빠 주머니에 들어갔대요
This accidentally fellinto my father's pocket.
괜찮아요
It's okay.
새라를 아끼셔서 그러는거잖아요
He's just beingprotective of you.
어젯밤에 제가 하는 말
다 들으셨는데 그럴만도 하죠
And after the wayI behaved last night, I can't say that I blame him.
아빨 그렇게 좋게 평가하는건
척이 좋은 사람이라 그런거예요
Chuck, you're attributinggood intentions to himbecause you're a good person.
뭔가 좋은 일도 하셨을거 아니예요
Well, he must have donesomething right.
이렇게 딸을 잘 키우셨으니까요
You turned out pretty good.
가요
Let's go.
비결은 그게 진짜 사고여야 한다는거야
JACK:The trick wasit had to bean actual accident.
얘가 끝내주게 잘했지
Angel here was the best.
의사까지도 얘 팔이
부러진 줄 알았다니까
She could make a real docbelieve that she hada broken arm.
그거야 진짜 부러졌으니까요
Uh, that's becauseI did.
딱 한번, 그것도 무장 트럭이
얼음에 부딪혀서 그런거지
One time--that's only becausethe armored truckhit a patch of ice.
신이 도우신거예요
Unforeseeableact of God, honey.
적어도 어렸을 때
즐겁게 보냈잖아요
At least your childhoodwas filled with excitement.
너만큼 즐겁게 보낸 애는 없을게다
No kid had as much funas you did.
최근에 일은 어떠세요
Um, so this latest, uh, score?
새라 말론
두바이에 다녀오셨다던데요?
Sarah said you were justin Dubai?
말해도 돼나?
Sure it's okay?
괜찮아요
절 믿으세요
Oh, he's fine.Trust me.
너야 항상 믿지
Always, darling.
절대 그걸 잊지 마렴
Never forget that.
쉐익이라는 부자 얘길 하던데요?
Something about, uh, a rich sheik?
I'm not a boastful man,Charlie,but this was myMona Lisa. 자랑하는건 아니지만, 찰리
나한텐 모나리자 같은 존재지
I'm not a boastful man, Charlie, but this was myMona Lisa.
그 사람이 미국인한테
뭐든 사고싶어서 안달이 났더라고
These oil guyswere justdying to buy anything American.
설마, 그건 아니시겠죠
Oh, no.You didn't.
아니긴
Of course I did.
무슨 말인지 못 알아듣겠어요
I think I'm missinga step here.
리튼슈타인 얘길 하신거예요
He pulled aLichtenstein.
리튼 뭐요?
A Lichten what?
리튼슈타인은 아빠가
만들어 낸 사람인데
Lichtenstein is a crazyinvention of my father's.
상황이 힘들어져서 뭐든 빨리
A German billionairewho has fallen on hard times,
팔아야하는 독일인 억만장자예요
and needs to sellsomething fast.
예술 작품이나 보석 같은거요
So, like, a piece of art, or jewelry?
더 큰거
Bigger.
배? 비행기?
A boat?A plane?
거의 맞췄어, 찰리
Closer, Charlie.
하지만 내가 머무는 호텔로 오라고
한건 다 이유가 있어
But I brought youto my hotel fora reason.
저걸 팔았거든
I sold them that.
네?
What?
나가미치 플라자를 파셨다고요?
You sold themNagamichi Plaza?
굉장하네요
That's incredible.
위험하잖아요
That's dangerous.
아빨 찾아낼거라고요
They're going to find you.
진정해
Oh, relax.
70만달러는 리튼슈타인하고
연결해주는걸로 받은 중개 수수료야
The 700 grandis a finder's feefor putting them in touchwith Lichtenstein.
사기란걸 알아차릴때쯤엔
난 섬에 가있을거야
By the time they know it's gone, I'll be on an island.
기억해둬, 찰리
큰 거짓말일수록 더..
Remember, Charlie, the bigger the lie, the easier...
더 쉽게 믿는다
The easier it is to believe.
좋아, 아주 좋아
Very good.Very good.
아버지가 우릴 커플이라
믿으시는것 같아요?
CHUCK:You think your dadbought us as a couple?
멋진 분이신것 같아요
He's a pretty sharp guy.
오늘 기분이 좋으시더라구요
He has his moments.
우리 스킨쉽도 좀 늘려야겠어요
Maybe we shouldamp up the PDA.
그래야 더 잘 믿으실거 아니예요
Try and sell ita little better.
참 재밌네요
Very funny.
지갑 잘 있나 확인이나 해요
Just make sure youhave your wallet.
떠올랐어요. 저 사람이예요
I just flashed.That's him.
쉐익 라지브 아마드요
That's Sheik Rajiv Amad.
- 여기 있어요
- 여긴 왜 온걸까요?
-Stay here.
-What do you thinkhe wants?
뭐겠어요?
What do you think?
리튼슈타인이죠
Lichtenstein.
있지도 않은 사람이라 안타깝네요
Too badhe doesn't exist.
뭔가 심각한 오해가 있었나봅니다
This, uh, this has allbeen a terriblemisunderstanding.
아침에 리튼슈타인씨
사무실에서 만나는건 어떨까요
Why don't wemeet in the morningin Mr.Lichtenstein'soffice
그때 다 해결하죠
and we can settlethis whole mess.
내가 바본줄 아는 모양이군요
You must think I'm a fool, Mr.Burton.
돈을 돌려주시죠
I want my money.
돈을 돌려달라구요, 알겠습니다
Well, you wantyour money back, that's fine,
하지만 그렇게 되면
거래는 끝나는겁니다
but I have to warn youthen the deal is off.
사실 여기 이 분이
리튼슈타인씨 개인 비서십니다
In fact, uh, this isMr.Lichtenstein'spersonal secretary right here.
애플범양?
Ms.Applebaum?
이쪽은 쉐익 라지브 아마드씨세요
May I presentSheik Rajiv Amad.
반갑습니다
It's a pleasure to meet you.
리튼슈타인씨께서 기다리고 계세요
Mr.Lichtenstein hasbeen expecting you.
내일 2시는 어떠세요?
How's tomorrow at 2:00?
더 좋은 생각이 있어요
I have a better idea.
지금 가서 만나는게 어때요?
Why don't we goget him right now?
그럴줄 알았지
I thought so.
리튼슈타인은 무슨
There's no Lichtenstein.
리튼슈타인씨?
WOMAN:Mr.Lichtenstein?
여기 리튼슈타인씨 계신가요?
Is therea Mr.Lichtenstein here?
네
Ja.
리튼슈타인씨,
메시지가 왔습니다
Uh, Mr.Lichtenstein, you have a message.
쉐익 라지브 아마드 씨
한스 리튼슈타인씹니다
Uh, Sheik Rajiv Amad, may I presentHans Lichtenstein.
안타깝게도 리튼슈타인씨는
독일어만 할 줄 아세요
Unfortunately, Mr.Lichtensteinonly speaks German.
하지만 내일 오후엔
만나실 수 있을겁니다
But he'll be happy to meet youtomorrow at his office.
2시 어떠세요?
2:00?
좋아요
Okay.
하지만 내 빌딩을 못 가지면
죽은 목숨인줄 아시오
But if I don't getmy building, he's a dead man.
통역해요
Translate that.
그럼 이만
AMAD:Okay.
둘다 사기꾼일줄 알았어
I knew you twowere on the grift.
네 아비는 못 속인다
You can't put onepast your old man.
자기, 우리 계좌에서
2500달러 뺀거 어디에 썼어?
Hey, honey, why is there$2, 500 missingfrom our account?
말한다는걸 깜빡했네
모건 빌려줬어
I forgot to tell you, I lent it to Morgan.
병원에서 다른
모건이라도 만났나봐
I can only assumethat you met some other Morganat work,
그 모건한테 우리 돈을
그냥 줘버렸단건
because the thoughtof you giving awaya hunk of our nest egg
생각하기도 끔찍하니까
is just too horrificto consider.
그냥 줘 버린거 아니야
I didn't give it away.
애나랑 아파트 구할 수 있게
빌려준거야
I lent it to himso he can get anapartment with Anna.
척, 모건이
바이모어에서 얼마나 벌어?
Uh, Chuck, how much does Morganmake at the Buy More?
시간당 12달러 정도
Uh, about 12 bucks an hour.
근데 항상 500달러쯤 되는
Not includinghis alwaysappreciating comicbook collection
만화책 콜렉션도 사 모아
which I would valuein the $500 area.
데븐 / 걔 미래에 한 투자였어
-Devon...
-It was an investmentin his future.
그럼 어른이 될까 싶어서
You know, so he couldbecome an adult.
아마 모건일꺼야
That would probably be Morgan.
출근길에 태워다 주기로 했어
He's giving me a ride to work.
뭐로? 자전거로?
On what, his handlebars?
아니, 모건이 겨우 움직이는
81년형 드로리안을 샀거든..
No, uh, uh, Morgan, Morgan bought a barelyfunctioning '81 DeLoreanthat...
1시간에 22마일밖에 못간다니깐
난 빨리 가봐야겠어
only goes 22 miles an hour, so I better get going.
이따 봐
See ya.
아무 말 하지마, 엘리
You don't have to say it, babe.
우리 돈 꼭 찾아올게
I'll get our money back.
장군님, 어제 밤 일은 죄송합니다
General, I'd like to apologizefor last night.
척이 저희 아빠 사기에
연루되지 않았어야 했는데요
Chuck never should havegotten caught upin my father'sridiculous con.
쉐익이 이 나라를
떠날 때까지 인터섹트를
I recommend we placethe Intersect inprotective lockdown
안전한 시설에
옮겨 두는게 좋겠습니다
till we're sure the sheikis out of the country.
그렇게 해서
완벽한 작전을 망치자는건가?
And waste the perfect setup?
무슨 말씀이신지 모르겠습니다
I'm not sure I follow.
CIA에선 몇년간 아마드 일가의
비밀 계좌를 알아내려했네
The CIA has been trying tolocate the hidden bank accountsof the Amad family for years.
자네한테 자금을
송금하게 만들수 있다면
If you can convince himto wire you the funds,
우리가 그 계좌를 동결시킬 수 있을거야
we can access those accountsand freeze them.
무슨 자금 말씀이세요?
Uh, funds for what?
빌딩 말이야
The building.
아마드의 해외 계좌에 접근하려면
적어도 10만달러는 되야해
It will need to beat least $10 millionto access his internationalaccounts.
장군님, 지금 저희한테
사기를 치란 말씀이십니까?
General, is the agencyasking us to commit fraud?
아니. CIA에 자네들 작전에 대한
정보가 있다는거지
No, that would mean the CIA hassome knowledge of your mission.
어떻게 하루만에
60층짜리 건물을 팔겠습니까?
How are we supposedto sell a 60-storybuilding in one day?
자네 아버지께 여쭤보게
Ask your father.
그 쪽 일에
능숙하신것 같으니 말이야
He seems to be very proficientin his chosen profession.
Wait, this is the soundcoming from here.
-Oh, that's...
-Yeah, you thoughtthat the...
모건 어딨는지 알아?
Do you know where Morgan is?
누가 말하던가요
Who's to say?
고급 플루토늄만 있었다면
If he was ableto get a hold of somehigh-grade plutonium,
어디든 있을 수 있죠
he could be anywhere.
어디든, 언제든지
JEFF:Any place.Any time.
옛 서부에 있을지도요
The Old West perhaps?
시간여행을 할 수 있다면
난 레스터가 태어날 때로 갈래
If I could travelin time, I'd go to Lester's birth.
질에서 나오는
네 얼굴을 보고싶어
I'd love to see the lookon your facewhen you emergedfrom the vaginal canal.
모건은 드로리안에 붙일 번호판때문에
자동차 관리국에 갔어요
Morgan went to the DMV to getplates for the DeLorean.
쓸데없는 차가 아니고
아파트 빌리라고 돈 빌려준건데
I lent him that moneyto get an apartment, not blow it on somestupid car.
뭐라구요?
What?
그 돈이 아파트 구할 돈이었어요?
That money wasfor our apartment?
죽여버릴거야
I'm gonna kill him.
줄부터 서요, 애나
Get in line, Anna.
자, 내 말 들어봐
All right, here's the thing.
둘 다 번호판 보고 나서 얘기해
I beg both of youto reserve judgmentuntil you've seenthe plate.
왜냐하면 이걸 보면..
'Cause you aregonna be.
Yeah.
괜찮죠?
I nailed it, right?
하루 줄테니까 내 돈 가져와
아님 온 몸을 뜯어버릴테니까
You have exactly one dayto get my money backto me or I pluck youfrom headto toe.
사타구니부터 시작해요
Start with the groin.
한동안 거기 쓸 일은 없을테니까요
He won't be using that regionfor a while.
하지만, 자기..
But, honey...
우릴 위해 산거야!
I got it for us.
지금와서 발 뺄 이유가 없잖아요
SARAH:There is no reasonto walk away now.
3%를 입금하게 할 수 있을거예요
You know, I think wecould get the sheikto pay a threepercent deposit.
시가가 30억 달러가 넘으니까..
Market value is over$300 million...
적은 돈이 아니야
That's a lot of dough.
잊지마렴 얘야
돼지가 살이 찌면 도살되기 마련이다
Remember darling, pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered.
큰 거짓말일수록
더 쉽게 믿으니까요
Well, the bigger the lie, the easier it is to believe.
할 수 있어요
We can do this.
한 사람당 500만 달러도
나쁘지 않겠지
I guess, uh, 5 mill eachain't too bad.
250만 달러예요
Two point five.
제 도움이 필요하시면
제 팀을 써야해요
You want my help, youhave to use my team.
무슨 팀?
What team?
얼굴이 꼭 경찰같잖아
He's got a cop face.
나쁜 뜻은 없어요
No offense.
아빠, 저 사람 안 끼면
우리 다 안해요
Look, either he's in, or none of us are.
알았어. 하지만
저 사람은 네가 알아서해
Fine.But he's your problem.
자, 거래는 나랑 새라가 맡을테니
All right, Sarah and Iwill handle the deal.
경찰 얼굴, 자넨 경호를 맡게
Cop Face, you're security.
원하면 이름 바꿔줄게요
We can switch namesif you'd like.
내가 '경찰 얼굴' 할테니까
케이시가 '바보' 해요
I can be Cop Faceand you can be Schnook.
송금은 우리 계좌로 하세요
We'll use our account numberfor the wire transfer.
당신 못 믿어요
Don't trust you.
나쁜 뜻은 없어요
No offense.
질문 있어요
전 뭐해요?
Uh, question--what about me?
제가 호건의 영웅들이나
캐슬 울펜스타인은 잘 알지만
I mean, I'm familiarwithHogan's HeroesandCastle Wolfenstein,
제 독어 실력이 좀 녹슬어서요
but beyond thatmy German is a little rusty.
바보 청년, 자네 일이 제일 어려울거야
Schnook, your job is goingto be toughest of all.
거기 앉아서 입도 뻥끗 안하면 돼
You need to sit thereand not say a word.
자, 모두 모여봐
All right, everybodygather around.
나가미치 빌딩 51층
첫째, 그 빌딩을 비워야해
(Nagamichi Building 51st Floor)
First, we needto evacuate the currentbuilding management.
잠시 주목해주시겠습니까?
Can I have your attentionplease?
모두 이 사무실을 나가주세요
We need everyone out of thisoffice immediately.
이 층이 소독중입니다
This floor is being fumigated.
유독가스를 이미 뿌렸습니다
We have alreadyreleased toxic fumes.
그로 인해 불임이나 정자 수의
감소 현상이 일어날 수 있습니다
That can lead to infertilityand low sperm count.
자 모두 들으셨죠
다들 나가주세요
All right, you heard them.Everyone out.
어서요 여러분
Let's go, people.
어서요. 서두르세요
Quickly.Quickly.
다음, 리튼슈타인 사무실로 꾸며놔야해
JACK:Next, we need to redecorateLichtenstein Enterprises.
경찰 얼굴
Cop Face,
나가미치 빌딩 로비
자넨 신이 주신 선물,
그 경찰 얼굴을 이용하게
(Nagamichi Building Lobby)
you're going to usethe gifts God gave you--your cop face.
도착했다
They're here.
시작하지
Showtime.
가장 중요한건 우리가 이 빌딩을
JACK:Most importantly, we need to convince him
팔고 싶지 않아한다는
인상을 줘야 한다는거야
that we don't wantto sell the building.
거래를 하고 싶어하는건
우리가 아니고 그 사람이야
He's the onegetting the deal, not us.
죄송합니다. 리튼슈타인씨는
금요일에 프라하에 계십니다
I'm sorry, Mr.Lichtensteinwill be in Pragueon Friday.
아뇨. 월요일엔 모스크바요
No, Mondayhe's in Moscow.
웬디, 난 방해받고 싶지 않아
JACK:Wendy, I don't wantto be interrupted.
트럼프씨가 전화를
하던 말던 관심없어
I don't careif Mr.Trump calls.
이제 이 빌딩 안 판다고
Tell him the buildingis no longer for sale.
다음 주에 뉴욕에서 보자고 전해
I'll see him next weekin New York.
여러분, 어서 오십시오
Gentlemen, welcome.
다음주에 다시 전화 드리겠습니다
SARAH:We'll haveto call you back next week.
안녕히 계세요
Bye-bye.
리튼슈타인씨께서 기다리고 계십니다
Mr.Lichtensteinwill see you now.
여러분, 한스 리튼슈타인씹니다
Gentlemen, may I present to youMr.Hans Lichtenstein.
다들 바쁘실테니
짧게 끝내도록 하겠습니다
JACK:Well, I'm sureyou're very busy, so we'll make thisas painless as possible--
변호사님이 거래를 검토하시고
조사가 끝나는대로
after your lawyersexamine the contractsand the inspectionsare done,
미팅을 여러번 더 갖도록 하죠
we can havea more formal meeting.
지금은 시장에 거래를 취소하기 위해
필요한 3%만 입금해주시면 됩니다
For now, we only requirea three percent depositto take the propertyoff the market.
그러면...
JACK:And that would be...
1000만 달러가 되겠군요
$10 million.
우선, 리튼슈타인씨와
얘길 나누고 싶군요
First, I would liketo have a wordwith Mr.Lichtenstein.
물론이죠
Of course.
제가 통역해드리죠
I'll translate.
아마드씨께서 얘길 나누고 싶으시답니다
************
미안하지만,
그 쪽은 믿을수가 없어요
I'm sorry.I don't trust you.
직접 통역가를 데려왔소
I broughtmy own translator.
안녕하세요, 리튼슈타인씨
Hallo, HerrLichtenstein.
하시고 싶은 말씀이 계시면
절 통해서 하시면 됩니다
Irgendetwas, dasSie sagen m.gen, sagen Sie durch mich.
이렇게 최악인
독일 억양은 처음 들어보네요
That is the worst German accentI have ever heard.
우리나라 말을 망치고 있잖아요
You...you butchermy language.
거래는 없던걸로 하겠어요
The deal is off.
꼭 코로넬 클링크 같군
('호건의 영웅들'에 나오는 배우 이름)
Sounds like Colonel Klink.
그니까 오늘 아무도 구제업자를
부른 사람이 없단 말이지?
MAN:So, as far as you know, no one orderedan exterminator today?
대체 무슨 일인지 알아보러
지금 가는 중이야
I'm on my way nowto find out what the hellis going on.
다시 돌아오고 있어
어서 끝내
We got company.Time to wrap it up.
죄송합니다, 아마드씨
I'm sorry, Mr.Amad.
거래는 끝난것 같네요
하지만 계좌번호를 알려주시면
It looks likethe deal is off, but if I could haveyour account number,
버튼씨께 주셨던 70만 달러를
송금해드리도록 하겠습니다
I'd be happy to wire youthe $700, 000that you gaveto Mr.Burton.
잠깐 잠깐 잠깐
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
놀라실 필요 없습니다
Now, there's noreason to panic.
다들 진정하세요
Everyone, calm down.
해결할 수 있을겁니다
We can work this out.
안돼! 안돼!
Nein, nein!
내 빌딩에서 나가
Out of my building.
거래는 끝났어!
The deal is off.
리튼슈타인씨께서 기분이
언짢으신것 같으니 모두 나가주세요
SARAH:Mr.Lichtensteinhas been offended.Everyone out of the building.
다들 진정하세요
There's no reasonto panic.
모두 사업가지 않습니까
다들 앉아서 잘 끝내...
Uh, we're allbusinessmen here.Let's just sit downand finish...
그만해!
Enough!
다들 미쳤군
You're all crazy.
장난은 그만해
No more games.
이건 내 빌딩이야
This is my building.
거래하기로 했잖소
We had a deal.
쉐익씨, 안전 문제 때문이니
Uh, well, Sheik, would you careto, uh,
계좌번호를 쳐주시겠어요?
type inyour account numberfor security purposes?
네, 어서 쳐주세요
Uh, just go aheadand do the typey type.
마음껏 둘러보세요
JACK:Feel free to lookover the space.
시간을 드리죠
We'll, uh, give you a moment.
독일인하곤 사업하면 안된다니까
Never do businesswith Germans.
당신들 누굽니까?
Who the hell are you?
여긴 어떻게 올라왔어요?
And how did youget up here?
벽엔 왜
리튼슈타인이라고 써있는거야?
Why does that wallsay Lichtenstein?
리튼슈타인을 위하여!
To Lichtenstein.
자네가 해낸거야
Well, you pulled it off, kid.
이젠 좀 믿을 수 있겠어
You made mea believer.
제 독일어 실력이 좀 녹슬긴 했지만..
Well, my Germanis a little rusty, but...
아니 아니
둘이 커플이란거 말이야
No, no, that you twoare a couple.
나중에 펴보게, 경찰 얼굴
For later, Cop Face.
승리의 담배인가요
고맙습니다
Oh, victory smoke.Thanks.
- 오늘 수고했다, 얘야
- 아빠도요
-You did good, baby.
-So did you.
가서 얼음 좀 가져오마
I'm gonna get some ice.
내가 뭐랬어요, 라고
말하고 싶진 않지만
Well, I'm not oneto say I told you so,
그래도 좀 괜찮지 않았어요?
but I think that worked outpretty good, now, didn't it?
아빠가 절 위해서 잘 해내신것 같아요
I guess he pulled throughfor me...
이번엔요
this one time.
네, 장군님
Yes, General?
임무 완수했습니다
Mission accomplished.
돈은 한시간 전쯤
CIA 계좌로 입금했습니다
The money was transferredto the CIA accountabout an hour ago.
장군님이 돈이 안왔다시는데
Beckman never got the money.
노트북이 없어졌어요
The laptop is gone.
내 담배도
So is my cigar.
과일이 다 떨어졌대서
초콜렛 크로와상 두개 사왔어요
They were allout of fruit, so I was forcedto bring upa couple chocolatecroissants.
그렇다면 어쩔 수 없이 먹어줘야죠
Oh, I guess I have no choicebut to take those off you.
들어와요
Come in.
괜찮아요?
You okay?
괜찮아요
I'm fine.
아빠야 어디선가 나타나겠지만
정말 안타까운건
My dad will turn upsomewhere, but, uh, I guessthe real crimeis
쉐익의 계좌를
동결시키지 못한거예요
that we didn't getto freeze the sheik's accounts.
아버질 믿으라고 했던거 미안해요
Well, I'm sorryif I pushed youinto trusting your father.
아빠한테서 배운게 하나 있다면
If there's one thing I learnedfrom my father,
실망할 준비가 되어있는거예요
it's be readyfor disappointment.
그리고 굳이 잘못이 있다면
그건 다 내 잘못이고요
And if it's anyone'sfault, it's mine.
아뇨 아니예요
No, it's not.
11년전에 우리 아버진
나랑 누나를 떠났어요
11 years ago, my fatherleft Ellie and me.
아버진..
He's a...
특이한 분이셨죠
he was an unusual man.
관대한 분이셨던것 같아요
I guess that's generous.
엔지니어셨고요
An engineer.
크리스마스 카드나
생일 축하 전화도 오곤 했는데
We used to get Christmascards and birthday calls,
언젠가부터 갑자기..
and then one year itjust...
안와요
it just stopped.
이유는 몰라요
I don't know why.
아는게 있다면 그게 내 잘못은
아니었다는거예요
What I do knowis that itwasn't my fault.
인정해요, 이걸 깨닫는데
엄청나게 많은
Granted, it took a significantamount of time and...
시간이 들었고 상담도
많이 받았어요. 하지만..
an incredibleamount of therapyto come to thatrealization, but...
아버지 잘못이지
새라 잘못이 아니란걸 알아야 해요
you need to know thatyour father's sinsare his and not yours.
아침 9시치곤 멋진 얘긴데요
That's pretty eloquentfor 9:00 a.m.
어쩌겠어요?
What can I say?
내가 똑똑한 바보잖아요
I am an articulate schnook.
내가 운이 좋네요
Lucky for me.
자네 혼자 있나?
BECKMANYou're alone?
네 장군님
Yes, General.
잭 버튼을 추적했어
We've tracked down Jack Burton.
귀도 머킨스라는 가명으로
시내 모텔에서 지내고 있네
He checked into a downtown motelunder the alias, Guido Merkins.
민감한 사항이란거 압니다
Well, I understand thesensitivity of the situation.
저 혼자 가겠습니다
I'll go alone.
케이시 요원?
Agent Casey?
네?
Yeah?
워커요원에게
유감이라 전해주게
Tell Agent Walker I'm sorry.
알겠습니다
Roger that.
내가 2500달러를 어디서 구해?
MORGAN:Where am I goingto find $2, 500?
찰스
Charles.
안녕, 친구
Hey, my man.
언제나처럼 멋있네
Looking wellas usual.
세상에 이..
Oh, my, and that...
냄새는..
that scent.
비온 후 해변의 냄새야
It's like the beachafter the rains.
이름이 뭐야?
What do you call it?
데오드란트
Deodorant.
뭐가 필요한데?
What do you want?
내가 네 미래 매형한테
돈을 좀 꿨는데..
I, uh...I needto borrow some moneyor your futurebrother-in-l's gonna...
온 몸을 뜯어버리겠대
pluck me from head to toe.
얼마나 빌렸는데?
How much we talking?
뭐 그리 많지는 않고
Um, not too much.
2500?
$2, 500?
뭐 그 정도
Give or take.
오늘 수고했다 얘야
You did good, babe.
너만큼 즐겁게 보낸 애는 없을게다
JACK:No kid had as much funas you did.
뭐야
What?
얘야, 미안하다
하지만 아빠가 다 설명할게
JACK:Baby, I'm sorry, but I got a perfect excusefor what happened.
무슨 얘긴지 듣고 싶네요
Well, I'd loveto hear all about it.
나중에 해주마
Some other time.
널 위해 그랬다는것만
기억해주렴
Just rember, I did it all for you.
감동적이군
AMAD:So touching.
가족상봉이구만, 감동적이야
Oh, so touching--family reunion.
자, 내 돈은 어디있지?
Now, where the hellis my money?
나한테 없어
I don't have it.
그렇다면 문제가 생겼군
Well, then, we have a real problem.
주면 안된다, 얘야
Don't give itto him, honey.
우리 아빠한테 무슨 일 생기면..
If anything happensto my father...
왜, 돈 더 뜯어내기라도 할꺼야?
What, you will con meout of more money?
아니
No...
죽여버릴거야
I'll kill you.
내 돈을 돌려줘
그럼 아무 문제도 없을테니까
Then, bring me what is mine, and we won'thave a problem.
알았나?
Okay?
한시간후에 다시 전화하지
I'll call you in an hour.
빌려줘서 고마워
Thank you somuch for this.
그럼
Oh, yeah.
잠시만 비켜줄래?
Do you mind?
비밀번호 때문에 그래?
Oh, I can'tknow your PIN?
원하면 내것도 알려줄게
I'll give you mine if itmakes you feel better.
그래도 지킬건 지켜야지, 모건
There are someboundaries, Morgan.
알았어 알았어
미안해
All right, all right, I'm sorry.
맙소사
Oh, my God.
맙소사라니?
"Oh, my God, " what?
돈이 없어? 괜찮아
Oh, you're broke, right?It's okay.
걱정할거 없어, 있잖아?
Don't feel bad, dude.You know what?
다른데 가서 빌릴테니깐
신경쓸 것 없어
There are placesI could use some grooming, so forget about it.
새라
CHUCK:Hey, hey, Sarah.
이게 실수가 아니라 CIA에서
내 공을 보상하는거라 생각하고 싶은데
Look, I hope thisisn't a mistakeand the CIA has decidedto compensate mefor my numerous actsof heroism...
나중에 얘기해요
Later, Chuck.
갑자기 나도 모르는 1000만달러가
but there happens to bean extra-- oh,
내 계좌에 들어와있어요
I don't know--$10 million in my ATM account.
네?
What?
우리 아빠가 왜 그 계좌에
그 돈을 넣어두겠어요?
Why would my fatherput the sheik's moneyin your account?
다시 한번 말하지만,
아버지가 준 돈인지 어떻게 알아요
Again, we're not so sure thatthis is coming from your father.
내 말처럼 CIA에서 주는걸지도 모르죠
I'm still clingingto the compensation theory.
돈 그대로 둬요
Leave it there.
괜찮은 생각이네요
You know, that'snot a bad idea.
하루에 이자만
2000달러는 될테니까요
It should earn a couplethousand a day in interest.
뭐하는거예요?
What are you doing?
어디 가요?
Where are you going?
개인적인 일이예요
It's personal.
워커 봤어?
You seen Walker?
네, 방금 더플백에 셔츠랑
무기 잔뜩 넣고 급하게 나가던데요
Yeah, she just leftin a real big hurrywith two duffel bagsstuffed full of T-shirtsand some serious firepower.
어디 가요?
Where are you going?
개인적인 일이야
It's personal.
모건 / 응 척
-Morgan.
-Yeah, buddy.
모건, 내가 돈 빌려줄게
Morgan, I'm gonnaloan you the money.
정말 고마워
Oh, thank you.
우선, 드모건 좀 빌릴게
급해서 그래
First, I need toborrow the De-Morgan.It's an emergency.
그래 물론이지
자 가져가
Oh, absolutely, yeah, yeah, yours, done.
무슨 일인데 그래?
What's up?
개인적인 일이야
It's personal.
조심히 다뤄줘, 친구
Treat her well, my friend.
거기서 멈춰
That's close enough.
내 것 가져왔나?
You have something for me?
아빤 어디 있지?
Where's my father?
없습니다
Nothing.
쏘지 마요! 쏘지 마세요!
Don't shoot!Don't shoot!
여기 돈 가져왔어요
I have your money right here.
안돼요!
Hey, no!
총 뺏어
Grab her gun!
리튼슈타인씨
와주셔서 고맙군요
Mr.Lichtenstein, thank you for joing.
저한테 드로리안 파시러 오셨나요?
Here to sell methe DeLorean?
여기 돈 가져왔어요
I have your money, okay?
지금 당장 송금해드릴게요
And I can wire it to youright now.
거짓말이면 저 여자 머리에
총알 박아넣을거야
If you're lying, I will put a bullet in her head.
계좌번호만 알려주시면 되요
All I needis your account number.
어서요. 저흰 어쩌다 잘못
끼어든 사기꾼들일뿐이에요
Please.We're just a coupleof bad con menwho got in way too deep.
아시겠어요?
돈 돌려드리고 싶다고요
All right?All we want to dois give you your money back.
그러니 돈 받으시고
저흴 보내주세요
Come take it and let us go.
쉐익의 계좌번호군
The sheik's account number.
괜찮은 계획인데, 바토스키
Decent plan, Bartowski.
물론 절대 칭찬해주진 않을거지만
Of courseI'll never tell him that.
자, 이제 돈 돌려받으신거죠
There.You haveyour money.
거래 즐거웠소
Pleasure doing business.
자 죽여
Now kill them.
뭐라고요?
What?
거기 꼼짝말고 있어
Hold it right there!
재무부에서 나왔습니다
U.S.Treasury.
아무도 움직이지 마
Don't anybody move.
올려보내
Send 'em up, boys.
잡았어
I got him.
리튼슈타인 잡았어
I got Lichtenstein.
어서
Come on.
Yeah,you're really... 케이시, 정말..
Yeah, you're really...
연기 열심히 하시네요
You're really selling it there, Casey.
지금 장난칩니까?
Is this a joke?
지원은 어딨소?
Where's your backup?
나야 먼저 올라온거고
I'm just the tipof the spear.
나머지 팀은 올라오는 중이오
Rest of the crew'son their way up.
이 사기꾼 놈들을
몇 달째 추적해왔지
I've been followingthese grifters for months now.
여러분들이 증언해주시면
You know, if you gentlemenwould be willingto testify,
무기 소지죄는 없던걸로 해드릴게
I'm surewe can get the weaponscharges dropped, hmm?
무기 버려!
Drop it!
안돼 안돼 안돼
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
무기 내려놓지 않으면
네 아비는 죽어
You lower your weapon, or I will kill your father.
아빠한테도 저렇게 하는데
너한텐 어떻게 할지 생각해봐
If I did that to him, imagine what I'll do to you.
어서 무기 내려
Drop your weapon!
아마드가 도망친다
Amad's getting away.
한시간에 22마일밖에 못 가요
Not at 22 miles an hourhe's not.
다 처리했어
CASEY:All clear.
아빠
Dad.
고마워요
Yeah, thanks.
근데 수갑때문에 좀 아프네요
Little rough withthe cuffs, though.
신고하던가
Call it in.
허공에 쏴도 됐잖아?
You didn't use blanks?
대체 다들 왜 이래?
What's wrongwith you people?
경상인데요 뭐
It's just a flesh wound.
81년형 드로리언
도난 신고를 하고싶은데요
I'd like to reporta stolen '81 DeLorean.
번호판은 D-E-M-O-R-G-A-N 이요
License plate isD- E-M-O-R-G-A-N.
아니요
No, this is...
장난 전화 아닙니다
this is not...this is not a prank call.
자네들이 수고해준 덕분에
Thanks to your efforts, we were able to freezenearly
쉐익의 해외계좌에서
거의 10억 달러를 동결시킬 수 있었네
a billion dollarsof the sheik's foreign accounts.
수고했네
Well done.
장군님
General.
안 좋은 소식이네
Now, to the unpleasant news.
워커 요원
오늘 5시에 횡령 혐의로
Agent Walker, we're sendinga unit to your hotelto pick up your father
호텔에서 자네 아버지를
체포할 예정이네
for the previousembezzlement chargeat 5:00 today.
작별 인사를 하고 오게
이상이야
Say your good-byes.That's all.
장군님
General?
버튼씨께서 돈을 압수하는데에
큰 공을 세우셨으니
As you know, Mr.Burton was invaluablein the seizureof these funds.
형량을 좀 줄여 주실 수 있지 않을까요
Perhaps that could lessenhis prison sentence.
검찰 측에서 그걸 감안할걸세
Prosecution will be made awareof that.
고마워
Thank you.
방금 무슨 일이 있었는지 알아
MORGAN:You're not goingto believe this.
경찰한테서 전화가 왔는데
The police just called.
누가 드로리안을 훔쳐갔대
The DeLorean was stolen.
모건, 너한테 얘기하려고 했는데..
Morgan, I've been meaningto tell you...
척, 무슨 뜻인지 모르겠어?
Dude, do you knowwhat that means?
차를 압수해야 한다고
They have to impound the car.
신차 값 만큼 보상해준대
I'm gonna getBlue Book value.
짱한테 돈 갚고도
만 달러나 남아!
I'll pay back Awesome, and I'll stillhave ten large!
나 이제 부자야!
Dude, I'm rich!
우리가 부잔거지
We're rich.
이젠 예쁜 집가서 살 수 있는거야
Now, we can move in togetherin style.
거실은 쉐비 시크로 꾸밀거야
I am doing the whole living roomin shabby chic.
사랑해 / 사랑해
-Love you.
-Loveyou.
Kiss.Kiss.
맛있어라
Yummy kisses.
언젠가는 어른이 되야 하잖아?
Well, you have to growup sometime, you know?
딱 적당한 여자에 적당한 때네
The right girl, the right time.
자랑스럽다 친구야
I'm proud of you, buddy.
고마워
Thank you.
모건, 오디오 실에 뭐가 들어왔는지 알아
Dude, you're notgonna believewhat just showed upin the Audio Install.
모건, 안돼
Morgan, no!
안돼 / 가자
-No.
-Yes.
그러지마
do not...
그냥 보는건데 나쁠건 없잖아
Well, it couldn't hurtto look, you know...
네가 잘 쏴서 다행이야
Boy, luckyyou're a good shot.
하지만 실력있는 사기꾼은
총이 필요없어. 왜냐하면..
But a good con man doesn'tneed a gun, and he can leave...
원하는 때에 떠날 수 있으니까요
Leave town whenever he wants.
알아요
I know.
아빠, 록키 로드 좀 사다주실래요?
Uh, Dad, can you getme some Rocky Road?
저쪽 모퉁이에 가게가 있어요
There's a storearound the corner.
물론이지, 얘야
Sure thing, darling.
왜 척 계좌에
돈을 넣어두신거예요?
Why did you put themoney in Chuck's account?
그 경찰 얼굴은 못 믿겠고
어디든지 넣어두긴 해야하잖니
I need to put it somewhere'cause I didn't trust Cop Face.
척은 믿으셨어요?
But you trusted Chuck?
내가 사람들을 읽잖니
그게 내 유일한, 진정한 재능이지
I read people.That's the onlyreal talent I got.
그 애가 절대 널
배신하지 않을거란걸 알았어
One thing I know--that kid would never betray you.
그 친구가 널 사랑한다는거에
1000만달러를 건거야
I made a $10 million betthat he loved you.
결국 내가 맞았잖니
Turns out I was right.
금방 돌아오마
I'll be back in a minute.
아빠?
Uh, Dad?
더블 스쿱으로 사다주실래요?
Can you make it a double scoop?
알겠다 얘야
Sure, darling.
안녕한가, 찰리
Hello, Charlie.
바보란 이름에 익숙해지고 있었는데요
I've kind of grown accustomedto Schnook.
나도 그렇네
So have I.
저기
I, uh...
거기 와줘서 고마웠네
I wanted tothank you for coming back
도망칠 이유를
수도없이 줬는데 말이야
when I gave you tenmillion reasons to leave.
하지만 남아있을
좋은 한가지 이유도 주셨잖아요
But one really good reasonto stay.
새라도 절 위해서
똑같이 해줬을거예요
And she would have done the samefor me.
그래, 그랬겠지
Yeah, I believe she would have.
난 운도 좋지, 새라가
괜찮은 바보를 만나서 말이야
Lucky for me, she met the right schnook.
저쪽으로 가셨어요
He went over there...
우리 딸 경찰 같은거지?
My daughter is somekind of cop, isn't she?
네
Yeah.
그런 셈이죠
Something like that.
참 잘 컸어
JACK:She turned out pretty good.
형편 없는 아버질 뒀는데도 말이지
Even with a lousy father.
잘 돌봐주게나
Take care of her.
최선을 다하겠습니다
I'll do my best.
괜찮아요?
You okay?
괜찮아요
I'm fine.
이거 입어요
Here.
곧 돌아오실거예요
He'll be back soon.
아뇨 안 오실거예요
No, he won't.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)